wapr.com 2012-06-08

# Privacy Policy

## Wapr Privacy Policy Highlights

This privacy policy explains how we collect, use and store your personal information. By visiting our website http://www.wapr.com, you accept the practices described in this policy. This privacy policy has been in effect as of July 09, 2010. Wapr.com is a product of Core Software Pvt Ltd.

This privacy policy applies only to this website. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices on any non wapr.com websites to which this site links or that links to this site.

Core Software Pvt Ltd respects your privacy. We only collect, store and use personal information so that we may continue to enhance our goods and services to the benefit of our customers and members. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. Information we may request includes your name, title, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, credit card details, customer preference information, as well as other similar personal information.

 **How we use the information we collect?**

We use the information we collect for various purposes, including:

  * to provide the services that we offer
  * to complete your purchase transactions
  * to provide the services you request including product support
  * to send you offerings by email or mail
  * to keep you informed about the status of your orders
  * to identify your product and service preferences, so we can notify you of new or additional products, services, and promotions that might be of interest to you
  * to notify you of product upgrades or provide other information concerning products you have purchased
  * to notify you of company news 

Please note that many promotions and mailings are completed well in advance, so you may continue to receive some offers after you ask us to stop sharing your information. We appreciate your patience in giving us time to carry out your request.

 **Information Use and Disclosure**

We use the information you provide to:

1) We do not sell, rent, trade, license or otherwise disclose your specific personal information or financial information to anyone. However, it's possible that we might acquire or merge with or be acquired by another company or that we might dispose of some or all of our assets. If that happens, your personal information may be disclosed to another company, but that disclosure will be subject to the privacy policy in effect.

2) To allow the purchase of goods and services, we must provide your credit card number to financial services corporations such a credit card processors and issuers.

3) We may share non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to a particular web page, or the size of an order placed on a certain date) with third parties such as advertising partners. This information does not directly personally identify you or any customer without your consent.

 **Privacy and Data Security**

Wapr.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. We use SSL encryption to protect your personal information online, and we also take several steps to protect your personal information in our facilities. Access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to your personal information to perform a specific job are granted access to your personal information. While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline. If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a sales representative over the telephone. As Wapr is a business network and offers features that enhance your network of contacts, your profile will be viewed by other members of the network based on your account privacy settings you set.

 **Core Software Pvt Ltd. only uses your personal information for specific purposes**

We may be required to disclose such information in response to requests from law-enforcement officials conducting investigations; subpoenas; a court order; or if we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also will release personal information where disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect ourselves or others. For example, we may share information to reduce the risk of fraud or if someone uses or attempts to use our Site for illegal reasons or to commit fraud.

 **Links to other sites**

While visiting Wapr.com you may link to websites operated by our business partners or other third parties. This does not mean that we endorse those websites. We do not make any representations or warranties about any website you may access through our website. They are independent from us, and we have no control over, or responsibility for, their information or activities. You need to make your own independent decisions regarding your interactions or communications with any other website. If you provide personal information at one of those sites, you are subject to the privacy policy of the operator of that site, not our privacy policy. We encourage you to read that policy before submitting any personal information.

 **Product Reviews**

You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your email address and geographic location. If you submit a review, your geographic location may be visible to other users (your email address will be kept private). Also, any personally identifiable information that you submit as part of the review can be read or used by other visitors to the site.We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.

You may opt-out of Wapr.com marketing lists at any time. Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Each time you receive an email from us, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" or stop receiving them. If you choose to "opt-out," we will stop sending you e-mails. Please note, however, that some e-mail promotions are prepared well in advance, so you may continue to receive offers after you have chosen to "opt-out." We appreciate your patience in giving us time to carry out your request.

 **Contact Core Software Pvt Ltd.**

Core Software Pvt Ltd is the sole operator of Wapr.com.

 **Updates to this Policy**

If we change or update this privacy policy, we will post changes and updates on this site so that you will always be aware of what information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this privacy policy from time to time so you will know if the privacy policy has been changed or updated. If you have any questions about the privacy policy, please contact us at 404 437 6655 or at [privacy@wapr.com](mailto:privacy@livebiznet.com) This e-mail address is being protected from spambots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it..
